(Leonard:)What did you mean when you said
you were going to miss me?
(Leonard:)I don't know.
You'll be gone and I'll notice.
Okay. Well, what about this?
What does this mean?
Wine, a credit card and late-night
television are a bad combination?
(Leonard:)All right, fine.
(Leonard:)What about that really long hug?
What did that mean?
(Penny:)That wasn't a long hug.
(Leonard:)It was at least five Mississippis.
(Leonard:)A standard hug
is two Mississippis, tops.
(Penny:)Leonard, I don't know what to tell you.
It was just a hug.
- Glad we cleared that up.
- Yeah.
- I guess I'll see you.
- Okay.
(Penny:)- Have a safe trip.
- Thank you.
(Leonard:)- Bye.
- Okay, bye.
[SIGHS]
It means I wish you weren't going.